<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Technic Constructs on Tabletop Treasures</title>
    <link>//tabletop.dreamwalker.games/docs/morrows-magnificent-marvels/bestiary/technic/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Technic Constructs on Tabletop Treasures</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="//tabletop.dreamwalker.games/docs/morrows-magnificent-marvels/bestiary/technic/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Technic Collector Bot</title>
      <link>//tabletop.dreamwalker.games/docs/morrows-magnificent-marvels/bestiary/technic/collector/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//tabletop.dreamwalker.games/docs/morrows-magnificent-marvels/bestiary/technic/collector/</guid>
      <description>Technic Collector Bot #  Collector Bots are designed for one purpose &amp;ndash; collect and study everything. These peaceful constructs don&amp;rsquo;t pose much of a mortal threat, since its stun gun is used solely to incapacitate a target, the only potentially lethal part is its claw slam, and even that would be accidental unless the bot is malfunctioning.
When it comes to living creatures, the bot&amp;rsquo;s primary directive is &amp;ldquo;catch, tag, and release,&amp;rdquo; using its claw slam to catch its target so that it can inject a tracking chip under the skin, then release it to observe and record its behaviors, and finally catch it later for additional study.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Technic Hydra</title>
      <link>//tabletop.dreamwalker.games/docs/morrows-magnificent-marvels/bestiary/technic/hydra/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//tabletop.dreamwalker.games/docs/morrows-magnificent-marvels/bestiary/technic/hydra/</guid>
      <description>Technic Hydra #  Like their organic counterparts, Technic Hydras have multiple heads that regrow when severed. Instead of fire, though, these creatures need a lightning attack to disrupt their nanotech and prevent regrowth.
Similar to the Myrmidons, the Hydra has the ability to focus its electrical energy into a single beam of lightning, though the Hydra&amp;rsquo;s is powerful enough to paralyze at range. The general consensus of those who study this creature (and live to tell about it) is that it uses this ability to aid in hunting and bringing down prey.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Technic Myrmidon</title>
      <link>//tabletop.dreamwalker.games/docs/morrows-magnificent-marvels/bestiary/technic/myrmidon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//tabletop.dreamwalker.games/docs/morrows-magnificent-marvels/bestiary/technic/myrmidon/</guid>
      <description>Technic Myrmidon #  Resembling a flying humanoid, even the aberrant Myrmidon can be a formidable foe. Its laser tentacles can paralyze its target, leaving the victim vulnerable to other attacks.
When fully functional, the Myrmidon is no laughing matter. As intelligent as most humanoids, with the power to create a force shield for extra protection, and to lash out with its tentacles or generate an electrical pulse to hit enemies at range, the Myrmidon can pose a real threat to anyone who stumbles upon one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Technic Spiderbot</title>
      <link>//tabletop.dreamwalker.games/docs/morrows-magnificent-marvels/bestiary/technic/spiderbot/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//tabletop.dreamwalker.games/docs/morrows-magnificent-marvels/bestiary/technic/spiderbot/</guid>
      <description>Technic Spiderbot #  More annoying than dangerous to anyone who has grown beyond a commoner, unless they swarm. And swarm they do. Spiderbots generally appear in packs of no less than four.
These creatures are about the size of a large dog, with a body resembling a scorpion. Pincers on the front lash out to attack those in melee, while the spiked tail can either lash out in a melee attack, or open up to reveal small laser guns to hit targets at range.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
