<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Table Top Treasures on Tabletop Treasures</title>
    <link>//tabletop.dreamwalker.games/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Table Top Treasures on Tabletop Treasures</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="//tabletop.dreamwalker.games/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>//tabletop.dreamwalker.games/docs/morrows-magnificent-marvels/bestiary/unique/caroliss/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//tabletop.dreamwalker.games/docs/morrows-magnificent-marvels/bestiary/unique/caroliss/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>//tabletop.dreamwalker.games/posts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//tabletop.dreamwalker.games/posts/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amiri</title>
      <link>//tabletop.dreamwalker.games/docs/morrows-magnificent-marvels/bestiary/unique/amiri/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//tabletop.dreamwalker.games/docs/morrows-magnificent-marvels/bestiary/unique/amiri/</guid>
      <description>Amiri #  One of Golarion&amp;rsquo;s iconics for good reason. We encountered her during her earlier days, when she passed through Carrion Hill in Ustalav, where she was the reining champion of the fighting pit there.
She&amp;rsquo;s quite the formidable foe, having stood toe-to-toe against our own Gorumite and nearly defeated him. In fact, she would have done so, were it not for his half-orcish tenacity.
They&amp;rsquo;re quite good friends now, with a gleeful, healthy respect for one another.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Iomedaean Gryphon Rider</title>
      <link>//tabletop.dreamwalker.games/docs/morrows-magnificent-marvels/bestiary/gryphon-rider/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//tabletop.dreamwalker.games/docs/morrows-magnificent-marvels/bestiary/gryphon-rider/</guid>
      <description>Iomedaean Gryphon Rider #  Sporting lighter armor than their ground counterparts, the Gryphon Riders of Castle Urion are mounted Knights serving as air support and long-range patrol of the castle and River Road.
Gryphons, however, are not mere steeds. As part of their training, Gryphon Riders must take an egg and incubate it as the Gryphon parents would, so that the hatchling imprints on the rider. The Gryphon remains loyal to the rider throughout their shared life, creating the deep bond and ability to act as a single unit that is required to perform the aerial acrobatics the Riders are known for.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Iomedaean Knight</title>
      <link>//tabletop.dreamwalker.games/docs/morrows-magnificent-marvels/bestiary/knight/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//tabletop.dreamwalker.games/docs/morrows-magnificent-marvels/bestiary/knight/</guid>
      <description>Iomedaean Knight #  The Iomedaean Knights serve as the guard and ruling class of Castle Urion in southwestern Numeria. As Knights of Iomedae, they embody the typical &amp;ldquo;knight in shining armor&amp;rdquo; ideal. Their steel plate and (typically) greatsword are crafted to appear nearly white, save for their red gold accents, and kept highly polished.
Variant: Defensive Defensive Knights forego the greatsword of most knights in favor of the more stereotypical longsword and shield, granting them additional protection at the expense of a little damage output.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Technic Collector Bot</title>
      <link>//tabletop.dreamwalker.games/docs/morrows-magnificent-marvels/bestiary/technic/collector/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//tabletop.dreamwalker.games/docs/morrows-magnificent-marvels/bestiary/technic/collector/</guid>
      <description>Technic Collector Bot #  Collector Bots are designed for one purpose &amp;ndash; collect and study everything. These peaceful constructs don&amp;rsquo;t pose much of a mortal threat, since its stun gun is used solely to incapacitate a target, the only potentially lethal part is its claw slam, and even that would be accidental unless the bot is malfunctioning.
When it comes to living creatures, the bot&amp;rsquo;s primary directive is &amp;ldquo;catch, tag, and release,&amp;rdquo; using its claw slam to catch its target so that it can inject a tracking chip under the skin, then release it to observe and record its behaviors, and finally catch it later for additional study.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Technic Hydra</title>
      <link>//tabletop.dreamwalker.games/docs/morrows-magnificent-marvels/bestiary/technic/hydra/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//tabletop.dreamwalker.games/docs/morrows-magnificent-marvels/bestiary/technic/hydra/</guid>
      <description>Technic Hydra #  Like their organic counterparts, Technic Hydras have multiple heads that regrow when severed. Instead of fire, though, these creatures need a lightning attack to disrupt their nanotech and prevent regrowth.
Similar to the Myrmidons, the Hydra has the ability to focus its electrical energy into a single beam of lightning, though the Hydra&amp;rsquo;s is powerful enough to paralyze at range. The general consensus of those who study this creature (and live to tell about it) is that it uses this ability to aid in hunting and bringing down prey.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Technic Myrmidon</title>
      <link>//tabletop.dreamwalker.games/docs/morrows-magnificent-marvels/bestiary/technic/myrmidon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//tabletop.dreamwalker.games/docs/morrows-magnificent-marvels/bestiary/technic/myrmidon/</guid>
      <description>Technic Myrmidon #  Resembling a flying humanoid, even the aberrant Myrmidon can be a formidable foe. Its laser tentacles can paralyze its target, leaving the victim vulnerable to other attacks.
When fully functional, the Myrmidon is no laughing matter. As intelligent as most humanoids, with the power to create a force shield for extra protection, and to lash out with its tentacles or generate an electrical pulse to hit enemies at range, the Myrmidon can pose a real threat to anyone who stumbles upon one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Technic Spiderbot</title>
      <link>//tabletop.dreamwalker.games/docs/morrows-magnificent-marvels/bestiary/technic/spiderbot/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//tabletop.dreamwalker.games/docs/morrows-magnificent-marvels/bestiary/technic/spiderbot/</guid>
      <description>Technic Spiderbot #  More annoying than dangerous to anyone who has grown beyond a commoner, unless they swarm. And swarm they do. Spiderbots generally appear in packs of no less than four.
These creatures are about the size of a large dog, with a body resembling a scorpion. Pincers on the front lash out to attack those in melee, while the spiked tail can either lash out in a melee attack, or open up to reveal small laser guns to hit targets at range.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wolf&#39;s Bane</title>
      <link>//tabletop.dreamwalker.games/docs/morrows-magnificent-marvels/mechanics/wolfsbane/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//tabletop.dreamwalker.games/docs/morrows-magnificent-marvels/mechanics/wolfsbane/</guid>
      <description>Wolf&amp;rsquo;s Bane #  The curse of lycanthropy doesn&amp;rsquo;t take over immediately; a full moon is needed to cement its hold over a person. Until then, a potion made of Wolf&amp;rsquo;s Bane can be used to cure the person &amp;ndash; but the cure comes with risks of its own.
The potion that can cure early stage lycanthropy is volatile and must be made from the highly toxic Wolf&amp;rsquo;s Bane flower, must be administered before the afflicted&amp;rsquo;s first full moon, and the potion is only good for one to two weeks (and therefore cannot be made ahead of time and stockpiled indefinitely).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
