<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Unique Creatures and Notable People on Tabletop Treasures</title>
    <link>//tabletop.dreamwalker.games/docs/morrows-magnificent-marvels/bestiary/unique/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Unique Creatures and Notable People on Tabletop Treasures</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="//tabletop.dreamwalker.games/docs/morrows-magnificent-marvels/bestiary/unique/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Amiri</title>
      <link>//tabletop.dreamwalker.games/docs/morrows-magnificent-marvels/bestiary/unique/amiri/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//tabletop.dreamwalker.games/docs/morrows-magnificent-marvels/bestiary/unique/amiri/</guid>
      <description>Amiri #  One of Golarion&amp;rsquo;s iconics for good reason. We encountered her during her earlier days, when she passed through Carrion Hill in Ustalav, where she was the reining champion of the fighting pit there.
She&amp;rsquo;s quite the formidable foe, having stood toe-to-toe against our own Gorumite and nearly defeated him. In fact, she would have done so, were it not for his half-orcish tenacity.
They&amp;rsquo;re quite good friends now, with a gleeful, healthy respect for one another.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Caroliss Minerran</title>
      <link>//tabletop.dreamwalker.games/docs/morrows-magnificent-marvels/bestiary/unique/caroliss/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//tabletop.dreamwalker.games/docs/morrows-magnificent-marvels/bestiary/unique/caroliss/</guid>
      <description>Caroliss Minerran #  Commander Caroliss Minerran leads the Iomedaean knights that rule the settlement of Castle Urion in Numeria. As such, she balances her oath to Iomedae, her deal with the Black Sovereign, and her own morals.
We ran into her when a vampire hunter came after me (long story), and it was her oath tenets of honor and compassion that saved us&amp;hellip;until one of my guys caused trouble at the inn later that evening (uh&amp;hellip;also a long story).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elvisar</title>
      <link>//tabletop.dreamwalker.games/docs/morrows-magnificent-marvels/bestiary/unique/elvisar/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//tabletop.dreamwalker.games/docs/morrows-magnificent-marvels/bestiary/unique/elvisar/</guid>
      <description>Elvisar #  One of the leading bards at the school in Castle Urion, he served as my bard tutor and loose ally while I was there.
He&amp;rsquo;s a little flamboyant (okay, a lot flamboyant), has a cocky streak, and gives truth to the bard stereotype, but behind the act, does genuinely care about those he calls friend.
   Elvisar #  Spring Eladrin College of Eloquence Bard 10, Chaotic Good</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
